Ion Nagurnea

Web Developer

Email: nagurneaion@gmail.com Tel.: 07564155466 Location: London

GitHub: https://github.com/IONnagurnea

LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/ionnagurnea/

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Highly motivated, energetic and self-disciplined person that likes to learn new things and improve constantly. With a background mainly in finance, looking for the first opportunity as Web Developer after finishing a year course for Full-Stack Developer with CODECADEMY involving PERN Stack technologies.

Please see my personal Full-Stack project on https://petlove-ion.herokuapp.com/ and related code on https://github.com/IONnagurnea/PetLove.

Main technical skills achieved:

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Bootstrap, MUI, ANT, REACT, Redux,

Node.js, Express, Rest API, Next.js, Mocha, Chai, Jest, Enzyme, Swagger.

Database Skills: PostgreSQL, MongoDb Compass.

Cloud Technologies: MongoDb Atlas, AWS, FireBase.

Serverless Technologies: MongoDB Realm.

Tools/Technologies/Utilities: Visual Studio 2022, Postman, Git control, GitHub, Powershell,

Microsoft Edge Developer Tools.

EDUCATION:

2021 – 2022: CODECADEMY, Full-Stack Engineer (2021 Version) - 144 Lessons, 80 Projects

Link to Certificate

August 2022: Udemy FullStack JavaScript React Node MERN eLearning Marketplace - 24h

Link to Certificate

February 2022: LinkedIn Learning Full-Stack JavaScript Development: MongoDB, Node, and

React (2016) - 3h 18m

February 2021: LinkedIn HTML Essential Training - 2h 45m

2017 - 2020: BSc (Hons) Finance, Investment and Risk at The London Institute of Banking

and Finance, Degree achieved 2:1

2016 – 2019: AAT Level 4, 3, 2

LEARNING PROJECTS:

Jamming bootstrapped with React - Github Link

Expense Tracker bootstrapped with React and Redux - Github Link

News Reader bootstrapped with React, Redux and MWS - Github Link

Codecademy Store bootstrapped with React and Redux - Github Link

Recipe App bootstrapped with React and Redux - Github Link

Reddit App bootstrapped with Create React, Redux, Redux Toolkit - Github Link

Add Quote bootstrapped with Node.js, JavaScript, HTML and CSS - Github Link

Server Side Rendering App bootstrapped with Node.js and React - Github Link

Restaurant Review with MERN stack - Github Link

WORK EXPERIENCE:

January 2021 - Present: SELF-EMPLOYED

Providing accounting services for self-employers and partnerships as well as providing security services while studying to complete the Full-Stack Engineer course.

February 2017 - January 2021: Finance Assistant at Pitman Training Group

<u>Company profile</u>: Pitman Training is the UK's leading independent training provider, offering self-paced vocational courses and diplomas.

Main Duties:

- Prepare balance sheets and journals.
- Create cost analysis reports (fixed and variable costs).
- Preparation and submitting quarterly VAT Return.
- Support monthly payroll and keep organised records.
- Provide support during budget preparation.
- Reconciliation bank statements and credit cards.
- Preparation and posting staff expenses.
- Reconcile any discrepancies or errors identified by conversing with employees and/or clients.
- Sage daily use / professional level.
- Process invoices and follow up with clients, suppliers and partners as needed.
- Collect and enter data for various financial spreadsheets.
- Record accounts payable and accounts receivable.

Additional skills:

- Proficient in Ms Word, Ms Excel, Ms PowerPoint, SAGE.
- Intermediate in SAS, SAP, Microsoft Dynamics AX, Ms Access, Ms Outlook
- Spoken/written languages: English (professional), Romanian (native), Russian (professional), Ukrainian (intermediate).
- Computer literate.
- Clean UK driving licence.

Other Certifications

CIMA Certificate in Business Accounting (CIMA CERT BA) (10/2020).

Financial Modelling & Valuation Analyst (FMVA) (05/2020 – 08/2020).

Bloomberg Market Concepts (05/2020), Bloomberg.

Trading & Financial Market Analysis Level 6 (10/2019), Amplify – The London Institute of Banking and Finance